Guide to the George Howard Edward Smith Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- SENATE REPUBLICAN POLICY COMMITTEE, 1932 -1960; Series III; 21 linear feet (57 boxes)
  - General correspondence
    - Biffle, Leslie L., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 197)
    - Bixby, R. Burdell, 1950 October (Box 7, Folder 198)
    - Bone, Hugh A., 1955 Nov, December (Box 7, Folder 198)
    - Boots, C. F., 1947 January (Box 7, Folder 198)
    - Borchard, Edwin (*), 1944-1947 (Box 7, Folder 199-200)
    - "Borrowed Staff", 1945-1948, undated (Box 7, Folder 201-204)
    - Brewer, Basil (*), 1949-1955 (Box 8, Folder 205)
    - Briggs, W. S., 1949 April (Box 8, Folder 206)
    - Brown, Hon. Clarence J., 1946 June (Box 8, Folder 206)
    - Burness, Jack, 1945 April (Box 8, Folder 206)
    - Burton, John E., 1948 October (Box 8, Folder 207)
    - Cain, Harry P., 1953 August (Box 8, Folder 208)
    - Caldwell, Louis G., 1944 May (Box 8, Folder 208)
    - Caphane, Walter C., 1948 August (Box 8, Folder 208)
    - Conscription News, 1945 November (Box 8, Folder 209)
    - Cooke, Edward F., 1953 February (Box 8, Folder 209)
    - Corsi, Edward, 1950 November (Box 8, Folder 209)
    - Cotter, Cornelius P., 1959 April - September (Box 8, Folder 210)
    - Cromer, Horace E., 1946 December (Box 8, Folder 210)
    - Danaher, John Anthony, 1945-1946 (Box 8, Folder 211)
    - Davidson, Eugene, 1948 Mar, April (Box 8, Folder 211)
    - Davie, Mrs. Preston, 1954 Oct, November (Box 8, Folder 211)
    - Davis, William. C., 1946 December 12 (Box 8, Folder 212)
    - Dawson, F. M., 1947 May 24 (Box 8, Folder 212)
    - Deschler, Lewis, 1946 December 13 (Box 8, Folder 212)
    - Dewey, Charles S., [1951] (Box 8, Folder 213)
    - Dirkson, Everett McKinley, 1946 December (Box 8, Folder 213)
    - Dixon, George, 1952 October (Box 8, Folder 213)
    - Donaldson, William J., 1947 January (Box 8, Folder 214)
    - Douglas, Paul Howard, 1950 March (Box 8, Folder 214)
    - Doying, George, 1947 September (Box 8, Folder 214)
    - Dozer, Donald M., 1951 Feb, March (Box 8, Folder 215)
    - Duke, Joseph C., 1949 May (Box 8, Folder 215)
    - Eaton, Charles A., Jr., 1946 December (Box 8, Folder 216)
    - Elliston, Herbert, 1949 May (Box 8, Folder 216)
    - Erdhardt, Leslie, 1946 December 1 (Box 8, Folder 216)
    - Fairchild, Fred Rogers, 1952 March (Box 8, Folder 217)
    - Ferguson, Myrtle (Jones), 1949 March (Box 8, Folder 217)
    - Flowers, R. L., 1946 December (Box 8, Folder 217)
    - Fossel, Leslie T., 1950 September (Box 8, Folder 218)
    - "Foundations for Foreign Affairs" (*), 1945 December - April (Box 8, Folder 219)
    - Galloway, Eilene-Marie (Slack), 1950 February (Box 8, Folder 220)
    - Galloway, George B. (*), [1946] - 1953 (Box 8, Folder 221)
    - Gallup, George, 1945 July (Box 8, Folder 222)
    - Glusman, Dan, 1955 January - February (Box 8, Folder 222)
    - Haas, Charles, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 223)
    - Hagerty, James C., 1956 (Box 8, Folder 223)
    - Hahn, Gilbert, Jr., 1947-1950 (Box 8, Folder 223)
    - Halleck, Charles A., 1949 May (Box 8, Folder 224)
    - Hazlitt, Henry, 1949 May 21 (Box 8, Folder 224)
    - High, Stanley, 1952 May (Box 8, Folder 224)
    - Hillings, Patrick Jerome, 1951 June (Box 8, Folder 225)
    - Hoffman, Clare E., 1945 March (Box 8, Folder 225)
    - Hoover, Herbert Clark, 1951 April (Box 8, Folder 225)
    - Hovde, Dr. Fred, 1947 April (Box 8, Folder 226)
    - Huber, Arista, 1951 June (Box 8, Folder 226)
    - Jackson, John E., 1951 February (Box 8, Folder 227)
    - Jacob, Doris A., 1946 December (Box 8, Folder 227)
    - Jeffery, L. W., 1950 May, June (Box 8, Folder 227)
    - Jewett, Frank B.m, 1946 January (Box 8, Folder 228)
    - Johnson, Robert L., 1951 April (Box 8, Folder 228)
    - Jones, Lloyd W., 1953 Jan, 1957 March (Box 8, Folder 228)
    - Kluttz, Jerry, 1947 June (Box 8, Folder 229)
    - Lawrence, William H., 1959 July (Box 8, Folder 230)
    - Legislative Reorganization Act (1946): Congressional Record, Daily Digest (*), 1946 March - 1947 July (Box 8, Folder 231-234)
    - Leighton, George, 1949 May (Box 8, Folder 235)
    - Leman, Al, 1952 October (Box 8, Folder 235)
    - Levine, Isaac Don, 1945 July - 1952 November (Box 8, Folder 235)
    - Lewin, Charles J., [1949] (Box 8, Folder 236)
    - Lewis, Fulton, Jr., 1945 October (Box 8, Folder 236)
    - Life Insurance Association of America, 1952 March (Box 8, Folder 236)
    - Loeffler, Carl, 1947 March (Box 8, Folder 237)
    - Long, Norton, 1953 February - May (Box 8, Folder 237)
    - McAdams, William D., 1948 May 18 (Box 8, Folder 238)
    - Macmahon, Arthur W., 1946 December (Box 8, Folder 238)
    - McNaughton, Frank, 1949 May (Box 8, Folder 238)
    - Martin, I. Jack, 1950 November - 1955 June (Box 8, Folder 239)
    - Measure, 1950 June - November (Box 8, Folder 239)
    - Megill, H. Newlin, 1949 February (Box 8, Folder 239)
    - Millikin, George, 1949 February (Box 8, Folder 240)
    - Murphy, William C., Jr., 1945 June (Box 8, Folder 240)
    - National Association of Manufacturers, 1946 March - April (Box 8, Folder 241)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc., 1955 June (Box 8, Folder 241)
    - National Citizens for Eisenhower Congressional Committee, 1954 July - August (Box 8, Folder 241)
    - National War Labor Board, 1945 August (Box 8, Folder 242)
    - Neumann, William L., 1945 December (Box 8, Folder 242)
    - Neville, George W., 1947 January (Box 8, Folder 242)
    - Nixon, Richard Milhous, undated (Box 8, Folder 243)
    - O'Brien, Dan, 1949 May (Box 9, Folder 244)
    - Oceana Publications, 1959 July (Box 9, Folder 244)
    - Office Magazine (*), 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 245)
    - Pearson, Drew, 1952 March (Box 9, Folder 246)
    - Pelly, Charline, 1945 July (Box 9, Folder 247)
    - Radigan, James P., Jr., 1952 June (Box 9, Folder 248)
    - Raish, Paul L., 1946 December (Box 9, Folder 248)
    - Rankin, Robert S., 1946 December (Box 9, Folder 248)
    - Reed, Daniel A., 1946 December (Box 9, Folder 249)
    - Regenery, Henry (*), 1945 November - 1949 June (Box 9, Folder 250)
    - Republican National Committee, 1945 July - 1955 January (Box 9, Folder 251)
    - Republican Senatorial Campaign Committee (*), 1944 June 1946 November (Box 9, Folder 252-253)
    - Republican State Central. Committee of Oregon, 1955 Dec, 1956 February (Box 9, Folder 254)
    - Reynolds, Walter L., 1951 June (Box 9, Folder 254)
    - Rice, ____, 1947 January (Box 9, Folder 254)
    - Richter, Frederick, 1946 October (Box 9, Folder 255)
    - Riddick, Floyd M., 1952 November (Box 9, Folder 255)
    - Robey, Rudolph, 1946 May - June (Box 9, Folder 255)
    - Robinson, Claude, 1949 May (Box 9, Folder 256)
    - Rogers, Lindsay, 1946 December 13 (Box 9, Folder 256)
    - "Science of foundation", 1945 October - 1946 June (Box 9, Folder 257-259)
    - "Science Legislation", [1945 Sep] - 1948 October (Box 9, Folder 260-268)
    - Scott, Hugh D., Jr., 1949 July (Box 9, Folder 269)
    - Shallenger, W, H., 1946 March (Box 9, Folder 269)
    - Simmons, Ed, 1949 June (Box 9, Folder 269)
    - Smith, Homer, 1946 October (Box 9, Folder 270)
    - Stricker, Adam K., Jr., 1957 April (Box 9, Folder 270)
    - [Taft Memorial] (*), 1953 October - 1957 January (Box 10, Folder 271-272)
    - Talbot, Joseph, 1950 October (Box 10, Folder 273)
    - Taylor, Robert G., 1950 December (Box 10, Folder 273)
    - Teeter, John H., [1945], 1946 (Box 10, Folder 273)
    - Thompson, Alyce (McGahan), 1949 May, 1952 November (Box 10, Folder 274)
    - Trice, J. Mark, 1949 February (Box 10, Folder 274)
    - U. S. Bureau of the Budget, 1945 April - 1947 April (Box 10, Folder 275)
    - U. S. Bureau of the Census, 1957 August (Box 10, Folder 275)
    - U. S. Bureau of Naval Personnel, 1946 December (Box 10, Folder 275)
    - U. S. Department of State, 1946 January (Box 10, Folder 276)
    - U. S. Federal Communications Commission, 1958 July (Box 10, Folder 276)
    - U. S. Federal Security Agency, 1948 April (Box 10, Folder 276)
    - Vandenbosch, Amry, 1951 June - July (Box 10, Folder 277)
    - Volgenau, Howard L., 1946 December 12 (Box 10, Folder 277)
    - Washington Post, 1952 October (Box 10, Folder 278)
    - Webb, William J., 1951 Oct, 1952 November (Box 10, Folder 278)
    - Weiss, Carol H., 1949 January (Box 10, Folder 278)
    - Westerfield, Ray, 1944 April - November (Box 10, Folder 279)
    - Willey, Grafton H., III, 1946 October (Box 10, Folder 279)
    - Williams, Harvie, 1958 April (Box 10, Folder 279)
    - Wilson, ____, 1945 April (Box 10, Folder 280)
    - Wolverton, Hon. Charles Anderson, 1945 April - 1947 May (Box 10, Folder 280)
    - Young, Roland, 1951 February (Box 10, Folder 281)
    - Zeller, Dr. Belle, 1950 November - 1957 January (Box 10, Folder 282)
    - Unidentified, 1945 Jul, 1953 Apr, undated (Box 10, Folder 283)
  - Party conference correspondence
    - Aiken, George David, 1949 May (Box 11, Folder 284)
    - Baldwin, Raymond Earl, 1949 May (Box 11, Folder 285)
    - Ball, Joseph Hurst, 1946 December (Box 11, Folder 285)
    - Barrett, Frank A., 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 285)
    - Beall, James Glenn, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 286)
    - Brewster, Ralph Owen, 1950 November (Box 11, Folder 286)
    - Bricker, John William, 1949 May, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 286)
    - Bridges, Henry Styles (*), 1945 January - 1960 February (Box 11, Folder 287)
    - Brooks, Charles Wayland, 1949 January (Box 11, Folder 288)
    - Bush, Prescott Sheldon, 1950 July - 1956 July (Box 11, Folder 288)
    - Butler, Hugh Alfred, 1945 July - 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 288)
    - Butler, John Marshall, 1955 April - 1957 June (Box 11, Folder 289)
    - Cahn, Julius N., 1949 May (Box 11, Folder 290)
    - Cain, Harry Pulliam, 1948 Mar, 1949 Feb,1952 November (Box 11, Folder 290)
    - Capehart, Homer Earl, 1949 May, 1955 March (Box 11, Folder 290)
    - Carlson, Frank, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 291)
    - Cooper, John Sherman, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 291)
    - Cordon, Guy, 1949 March (Box 11, Folder 291)
    - Dompierre, Oliver J., 1952 June - 1954 October (Box 11, Folder 292)
    - Donaldson, Ray S., 1949 May (Box 11, Folder 292)
    - Donnell, Forest C., 1945 July (Box 11, Folder 292)
    - Ecton, Zales Nelson, 1949 May, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 293)
    - Egen, Frances, 1950 February (Box 11, Folder 293)
    - Egenroad, Charles L., 1949 May (Box 11, Folder 293)
    - Ferguson, Homer (*), 1946 March - 1955 March, n. (Box 11, Folder 294-303)
    - Flanders, Ralph Edwards, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 304)
    - Gleason, James, 1958 April (Box 11, Folder 305)
    - Goldwater, Barry Morris, 1952 November - 1959 July (Box 11, Folder 305)
    - Griswold, Dwight Palmer, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 305)
    - Hickenlooper, Bourke Blakemore, 1946 June (Box 11, Folder 306)
    - Hruska, Roman Lee, 1955 April (Box 11, Folder 306)
    - Hart, Thomas Charles, 1946 May (Box 11, Folder 307)
    - Hendrickson, Robert Clymer, 1950 August (Box 11, Folder 307)
    - Hermann, Albert B., 1949 May (Box 11, Folder 307)
    - Ives, Irving McNeil, 1949 Apr, 1950 May, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 308)
    - Jenner, William Ezra, 1947 January - 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 309)
    - Kem, James Preston, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 310)
    - Kennedy, Lorne, 1949 May, 1950 May (Box 11, Folder 310)
    - Kenney, Jerry, 1954 April - May (Box 11, Folder 310)
    - Knowland, William Fife, 1949 May - 1955 April (Box 11, Folder 311)
    - Langer, William, 1949 May, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 312)
    - Lecompte, Karl Miles, 1947 July (Box 11, Folder 312)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 312)
    - McCarthy, Joseph Raymond, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 313)
    - Malome, George Wilson, 1949 June - 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 313)
    - Martin, Edward, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 313)
    - Martin, I. Jack, 1949 Jan, 1950 March (Box 11, Folder 314)
    - Millikin, Eugene Donald (*), 1945 January - 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 315)
    - Mitchell, D. J., 1954 March - November (Box 11, Folder 316)
    - Morse, Wayne Lyman, 1949 May (Box 11, Folder 316)
    - Morton, Thruston Ballard, 1959 June (Box 11, Folder 316)
    - Payne, Frederick George, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 317)
    - Potter, Charles Edward, 1952 November (Box 11, Folder 317)
    - Powell, Wesley, 1949 May (Box 11, Folder 317)
    - Purtell, William Arthur, 1952 Nov, 1953 Jun, 1958 August (Box 11, Folder 318)
    - Reed, Clyde Martin, 1949 May 16 (Box 11, Folder 319)
    - Reed, William R. (*), 1949 May [1950 Nov] (Box 11, Folder 320-321)
    - Reed, William T., 1950 February - March (Box 12, Folder 322)
    - Revercomb, William Chapman, 1946 February (Box 12, Folder 322)
    - Saltonstall, Leverett, 1947 Jul, 1950 August (Box 12, Folder 323)
    - Schoeppel, Andrew Frank, 1950 September (Box 12, Folder 323)
    - Seaton, Frederick Andrew, 1952 September (Box 12, Folder 323)
    - Smith, Mrs. Helen M., 1955 October (Box 12, Folder 324)
    - Smith, Howard Alexander, 1947 May, 1952 November (Box 12, Folder 324)
    - Taft, Robert Alphonso (*), 1944 April - 1953 (Box 12, Folder 325-329)
    - Thye, Edward John, 1949 May, 1952 November (Box 12, Folder 330)
    - Tobey, Charles William, 1949 January (Box 12, Folder 330)
    - Vandenberg, Arthur Hendrick, 1944, 1946, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 331)
    - Watkins, Arthur Vivian, 1949 Mar, 1952 November (Box 12, Folder 332)
    - Wherry, Kenneth Spicer, 1945 April - 1951 February (Box 12, Folder 332)
    - White, Wallace Humphrey, Jr., 1946 Jul, November (Box 12, Folder 332)
    - Wiggens, Chet, 1958 April (Box 12, Folder 333)
    - Wiley, Alexander, 1949 Apr, 1952 May (Box 12, Folder 333)
    - Williams, John James, 1949 May, 1952 November (Box 12, Folder 333)
    - Willis, Raymond Eugene, 1946 February (Box 12, Folder 334)
    - Wilson, George Allison, 1946 Jan, 1953 February (Box 12, Folder 334)
    - Circular letters (*), 1944 April - 1953 October (Box 12, Folder 335)
    - Circular memoranda
      - 1944 April - 1950 March (Box 13, Folder 336-359)
      - 1950 April - 1960 January (Box 14, Folder 360-374)
  - Blue cover staff handbooks
    - "Summary Report on Great Lakes...", 1944 November (Box 15, Folder 375)
    - "Facts and Opinions on Reciprocal Trade Agreements", 1945 May (Box 15, Folder 376)
    - "Public Policy in Postwar Aviation", 1945 June (Box 15, Folder 377)
    - "Wartime Record of Strikes and Lockouts", 1946 January (Box 15, Folder 378)
    - "Pros and Cons on Universal (Box 15, Folder 379)
    - Compulsory Military Training", 1946 January (Box 15, Folder 379)
    - "Foreign Loans: Miscellaneous Material", 1946 March (Box 15, Folder 380)
    - "Report on National Citizens Political Action Committee...", 1946 April (Box 15, Folder 381)
    - "OPA: Excerpts from House and Senate Hearings...", 1946 June (Box 15, Folder 382)
    - "Resume of Nominations by President Truman", 1946 August (Box 15, Folder 383)
    - "War Assets Administration and Surplus Property Disposal", 1946 September (Box 15, Folder 384)
    - "Government Spending and Lending at Home and Abroad", 1946 October (Box 15, Folder 385)
    - "Government Propaganda", 1946 October (Box 16, Folder 386)
    - "Freedom vs. Control...", 1946 October (Box 16, Folder 387)
    - "Labor Relations Stabilization and the Administration", 1946 October (Box 16, Folder 388)
    - "Unification of the Armed Forces", 1947 January (Box 16, Folder 389)
    - "Pros and Cons on Universal Compulsory Military Training", 1947 March (Box 16, Folder 390)
    - "The Story of the Eightieth Congress, First Session", 1947 August (Box 16, Folder 391)
    - "Summary Report on the Great Lakes...", 1948 Jan (Box 16, Folder 392)
    - "Observations on Government Revenues and Taxations...", 1948 February (Box 16, Folder 393)
    - "Republican Principles and Achievements. of the 80th Congress", 1948 March (Box 16, Folder 394)
    - "Observations on Investigating the Misconduct of Officials...", 1948 April (Box 16, Folder 395)
    - "Resume of Nominations by President Truman", 1948 May (Box 16, Folder 396)
    - "Excerpts from Hearings of Senate and House Banking and Currency Committees...", 1948 August (Box 17, Folder 397)
    - "The Story of the 80th Congress", 1948 September (Box 17, Folder 398)
    - "1948 Election Report", 1948 December (Box 17, Folder 399)
    - "Analysis of the Latest Crises in American Foreign Policy...", 1949 (Box 17, Folder 400)
    - "The Compulsory Health Insurance Issue", 1949 October (Box 17, Folder 401)
    - "Statements by Farm Leaders and Farm Economists Opposing the Brannan Plan", 1950 May (Box 17, Folder 402)
    - "Working Kit on Ten Campaign Issues", 1950 September (Box 17, Folder 403)
    - "Compendium of Material on the Ouster of General MacArthur...", 1951 April (Box 17, Folder 404)
    - "Controls: Timetable on Tardy Tactics by Truman", 1951 July (Box 17, Folder 405)
    - "Foreign Aid", 1951 August (Box 17, Folder 406)
    - "Lessons in Political Mythology...", [1952?] (Box 17, Folder 407)
    - "Looking Ahead in Congress...", 1952 January (Box 17, Folder 408)
    - "Materials for Reports to the People in Lincoln Day Speeches...", 1952 February (Box 18, Folder 409)
    - "Communism in Government...", 1952 August (Box 18, Folder 410)
    - "Secrecy in Government...", 1952 September (Box 18, Folder 411)
    - "Capsule Commentaries on the Democratic Administration", 1952 September (Box 18, Folder 412)
    - "Rights Guaranteed by the Taft-Hartley Act", 1952 September (Box 18, Folder 413)
    - "A Vote for Stevenson Is a Vote for Truman", 1952 October (Box 18, Folder 414)
    - "Senate Rules and the Senate as a Continuing Body", 1953 January (Box 18, Folder 415)
    - "Major Study and Advisory Groups of the Republican Administration, 1953 December (Box 18, Folder 416)
    - "The Republican Party--"Its Philosophy and Achievements", 1954 January (Box 18, Folder 417)
    - "What the Democrats said and Did Then-- What They Are Saying and Doing Now", 1954 March (Box 18, Folder 418)
    - "Summaries of Major Legislation Enacted by Republican 83d Congress", 1954 August (Box 18, Folder 419)
    - "The Dixon-Yates Proposal", 1954 September (Box 18, Folder 420)
    - "Cleaning Up the Mess: An Ugly Inheritance", 1954 October (Box 18, Folder 421)
    - "The Scandal of Scandals...", 1954 October (Box 18, Folder 422)
    - "Policy Differences between the Two Major Parties...", 1955 January (Box 18, Folder 423)
    - "Highlights on the Yalta Papers and Related Data", 1955 March (Box 18, Folder 424)
    - "Hell's Canyon: A National Issue...", 1955 April (Box 18, Folder 425)
    - "A, B, C's of Republican and Democratic Income Tax Records", 1955 May (Box 18, Folder 426)
    - "The Power of Congress to Require Testimony...", 1955 August (Box 18, Folder 427)
    - "Labor Union Political Expenditures", 1955 November (Box 18, Folder 428)
    - "Rights Guaranteed by the Taft-Hartley Act", 1956 April (Box 19, Folder 429)
    - "Senate Committee on Social Security--Background Information", 1956 May (Box 19, Folder 430)
    - "Fallacy of Democratic Claim to be 'Party of Common Man'", 1956 June (Box 19, Folder 431)
    - "Bipartisan Boards and Commissions", 1956 June (Box 19, Folder 432)
    - "The Republican Administration-- Principles, Policies and Objectives", 1957 February (Box 19, Folder 433)
    - "Americans for Democratic Action", 1958 April (Box 19, Folder 434)
    - "The Labor Bosses-- America's Third Party", 1958 July (Box 19, Folder 435)
    - "Leaves from the Lincoln Calendar...", [1959 Jan?] (Box 19, Folder 436)
    - "ABC's of U. S. Foreign Policy, 1945-1960...", 1960 May (Box 19, Folder 437)
    - "National Policies and Legislative Trends...", undated (Box 19, Folder 438)
    - "ABC's of Area Redevelopment" (cover letter), 1959 March (Box 19, Folder 439)
  - Articles
    - Numerical
      - 1-143, 1944 May - 1946 October (Box 20, Folder 440-473)
      - 144-300, 1946 October - 1949 January (Box 21, Folder 474-507)
    - Chronological
      - 1947 Mar - 1951 (Box 22, Folder 508-512)
      - 1952 Apr - 1959 Sep (Box 23, Folder 513-542)
  - Election campaign handbooks
    - "Working Kit on Ten Campaign Issues", 1950 September (Box 24, Folder 543)
    - General, 1950 September - November (Box 24, Folder 544-552)
    - Supporting material
      - Issue no. 2, 1950 September - October (Box 24, Folder 553-557)
      - Issue no. 3, 1950 October (Box 24, Folder 558)
      - Issue no. 4, 1950 October (Box 24, Folder 559-560)
      - Issue no. 5, 1950 September - October (Box 24, Folder 561-566)
      - Issue no. 6, 1950 October (Box 24, Folder 567-568)
      - Issue no. 7, 1950 October (Box 24, Folder 569)
      - Issue no. 9, 1950 September (Box 24, Folder 570)
    - Background material
      - "Major Issues of 1952" (Box 24, Folder 571)
      - "Election Issues of 1956" (Box 24, Folder 572-573)
      - "Background Information on Legislative matters", 1958 April (Box 25, Folder 574)
  - Senate Minority/Majority Memos and News
    - "Minority Memos"
      - Volume I
        - 1-34, 1952 February - September (Box 26, Folder 575-580)
        - 36-42, 1952 October (Box 26, Folder 581)
        - 36, 38, 1954 September (Box 26, Folder 582)
      - Volume II
        - 28, 29 (incomplete), 1960 August (Box 26, Folder 583)
        - 31, 1960 September (Box 26, Folder 584)
      - Indexes
        - Volumes I and II, 1952 February - 1960 September (Box 26, Folder 585-587)
      - Supplements
        - Volumes I and II, 1953 October - 1955 March (Box 26, Folder 588-594)
    - "Minority News"
      - 1-11, 1946 September - November (Box 26, Folder 595-597)
    - "Majority News"
      - 1-20, 1948 February - June (Box 26, Folder 598-602)
      - 21-37, 1948 July - October (Box 27, Folder 603-606)
    - "Senate Week in Review"
      - 1950 January - February (Box 27, Folder 607)
      - 1951 Feb, - October (Box 27, Folder 608-616)
      - 1953 June (Box 27, Folder 617)
  - Subject files
    - General
      - Ferguson, Homer: 1954 election
        - Biographical data, 1950-1954 (Box 28, Folder 618)
        - Leaflets, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 619)
        - Memoranda, 1949-1954, undated (Box 28, Folder 620-623)
        - Clippings, 1954-1955 (Box 28, Folder 624-625)
        - Press Releases, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 626-627)
        - Schedules, 1954 October - November (Box 28, Folder 628)
        - Speeches, 1947 June - 1954 August (Box 28, Folder 629-637)
        - Speeches, 1954 September - [1954] (Box 29, Folder 638-641)
        - Statements for Radio and Television, 1951 September - 1954 (Box 29, Folder 642-646)
      - Legislative Reorganization Act (1946)
        - Appointment of Senate Policy Committees, 1941 December - [1947] (Box 29, Folder 647-649)
        - Daily Digest of Legislative Proceedings, 1946 December - 1947 April (Box 29, Folder 650-651)
      - Taft, Robert Alphonso
        - Election, campaign material, 1947 June - 1948 May (Box 29, Folder 652-653)
        - Memorial foundation, 1953 July - 1959 April (Box 29, Folder 654-656)
    - Special reference files
      - Administrative power, 1945-1946 (Box 30, Folder 657)
      - Big government, 1947-1949 (Box 30, Folder 658-659)
      - "Borrowed staff", 1943-1945 (Box 30, Folder 660-667)
      - Bridges, H. Styles, 1955-1959 (Box 30, Folder 668-670)
      - Candidate organization, 1951-1954 (Box 30, Folder 671)
      - Candidates for all future primaries, [1948] (Box 30, Folder 671A)
      - Civil rights, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 672)
      - Communism, 1946-1950 (Box 31, Folder 673)
      - Congress
        - General, 1946-1960 (Box 31, Folder 674-685)
        - Articles, 1934-1939 (Box 31, Folder 686)
        - Articles, 1941-1945 (Box 32, Folder 687-688)
        - Cloture, 1948-1951 (Box 32, Folder 689)
        - Eighty-first, 1947-1950 (Box 32, Folder 690)